Guide to the James A. Roberts Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1999-290
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04492 Placer CEQA (Box 52, Folder 43)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04692 B&J Drop Box (Box 52, Folder 44)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 04992 Lancaster Landfill (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 05292 Keelung (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 05392 Townsend Pro Bono (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 05193 Green Valley (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - GEMS accounts payable: File Index (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - GEMS accounts payable: charge accounts (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - GEMS accounts payable: Amex corporate account (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - GEMS accounts payable: Checks received (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - GEMS accounts payable: Bad Debts (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - GEMS accounts payable: Bills Outstanding (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - GEMS accounts payable: Roberts (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - GEMS accounts payable: Wessel (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - GEMS accounts payable: Turkiewicz (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - GEMS accounts payable: MacKenzie (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - GEMS accounts payable: Roberts (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - GEMS accounts payable: MacKenzie (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - GEMS accounts payable: A-Z (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - GEMS accounting: Filing forms (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - GEMS accounting: W-95 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - GEMS accounting: Miscellaneous tax forms (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Hazardous Waste publications (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Wetland/Water publications (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Waste publications (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Nevada County reports (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Pittsburgh EIR 1994 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - California Environmental Services SoQ 1994 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Denmark A2 1991 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Denmark A3 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Denmark A4 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Denmark A5 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - GEMS proposals: P-95012 Ski & Rec (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - GEMS proposals: 91024.2 ETP Followup (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - GEMS proposals: P-95020 Yurok & Klamath (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - GEMS proposals: P-96009 Hawaii Geothermal (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - GEMS proposals: P-96013 Colombia EIS (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - GEMS proposals: P-96017 Florida Canyon Mining (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - GEMS proposals: 97009 China (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - GEMS proposals: P-97018 Mather Lake (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - GEMS proposals: CSHPC (California Heritage Preservation Commission) (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - GEMS proposals: Ecotourism Panel (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - GEMS proposals: U.S. Postal Service Facilities Environmental Guide 1997 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Certification: C-2 REA registration (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Certification: Background: People, other consultants (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Certification: Hargrove (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Certification: Clarke (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Certification: Roberts resume (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Certification: 000 File Index (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Certification: Teaching Experience (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Certification: Cressey-Aquatic (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Certification: Hines- MacKenzie resumes (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Certification: Wessel resume (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Certification: Fernandez (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Certification: Griggs (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Certification: Hoellwarth (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Certification: Knapp (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Certification: Jay Roberts 2008 resume (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Certification: Voss (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Certification: 95010 Zhong Wu (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Certification: Wood consultant (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Certification: CEQA (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - Certification: 300C CEQA Experience (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - Certification: 300C Coastal Experience (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - Certification: 300D Development projects (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - Certification: 300D Document Preparation (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - Certification: 300E Energy Experience (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - Certification: 300N NEPA/CEQA Experience (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - Certification: 300E Education (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - Certification: 300E Education coastal Planning (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - Certification: 300E Education EIA 2 Day (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - Certification: 300E Education EIA 3 Day (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - Certification: 300E Education EIA 4 Day (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Certification: 300E Education EIA 5 Day (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Certification: 300E Education Environmental Ethics (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Certification: 300E Education EIA Writing (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Certification: 300E Education Mitigation Monitoring (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Certification: 300E Education New Business Europe (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Certification: 300E Education EIA Handouts (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Certification: 300E Education Environmental Coordination (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Certification: 300E Education Environmental Management (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Certification: 300G General Rep. Project (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Certification: 300G Geo-Specific Alaska (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Certification: 300G Geo-Specific Asia (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Certification: 300G Geo-Specific Hawaii (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Certification: 300G Geo-Specific Mexico (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Certification: 300G Geo-Specific Tahoe (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Certification: 300G Geo-Specific (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - Certification: 300N NEPA experience (Box 55, Folder 58)
  - Certification: 300I International experience (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - Certification: 300P Parks & Rec experience (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - Certification: 300P Permit assistance (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Certification: 300P Proposal Preparation (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Certification: 300P Public Participation (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Certification: 300R Restoration (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Certification: 300R Risk (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Certification: 300S Standards (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Certification: 300U University Experience (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Certification: 300S Site Planning (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Certification: 300W Waste Management Experience (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Certification: 300U Urban Setting (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Certification: 300W Water Resources (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Certification: References (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Certification: Standard Fee Schedule (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Certification: Federal Maximum Per Diem Guide (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Certification: Federal Form 254-255 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Roberts personal and professional journals (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - UTR Conceptual Design Report 1996 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - UTR miscellaneous publications (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - EDCWA EIR Draft Final Supplement (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - 00690 Folsom 1987-1993: Broadstone EIR (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - 00690 Folsom Initial Study (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - 00690 Folsom Notice of Preparation 1991 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - 00690 Folsom RFP (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - 00690 Folsom Master (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - 00690 Silverbrook 6 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - 00690 #7 Folsom Office (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - 00690 Creekside (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - 00690.9 Oak Ave. Rezone (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - 00690.10 Willow Springs (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - 00690.11 Old Town Square (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - 00690.12 Dunmore Elderly Homes (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - 00690.13 Cobble Hills Ridge (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - 00690.14 American River Canyon (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - 00690.14 American River Canyon (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - 00690.15 Natoma St. Lot 6 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - 00690.16 Wetlands Seminar (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - 00690.17 Lot J (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - 00690.18 Arco (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93030 City of Weed (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 92029 NAS Application (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93001 Hydrovia Project EIA (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93002 FIG Symposium 1993 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93003 Taiwan Coastal (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93005 COE BOA (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93007 Norway (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93008 Golder Alameda (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93009 AES: Cogen (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93011 Courses (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93012 General Assistance to Administration (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93013 General Assistance to Director General (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93015 Yushan Forest Restoration (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93016 Kinmen Isle Military Monument (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93018 Legislative Yuan (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93017 Hualien University (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93020 RHAA Fremont (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93021 UC San Joaquin EIR (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93024 Corps of Engineers, Japan (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93027 Roseville RFP (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93029 Da Lin Pu Landfill (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93030 Victor Su (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93039 PNL Base Closure (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93036 Tung Kang River (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93037 Hollister Hills (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - GEMS proposals 1993: 93033 Pan Am Satellite (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - 7023 MCP: File Index (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - 7023.48 Legislation (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - 7023.49 FEMA/SF (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - 7023.50 Garaventa CCET (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - 7023.51 ICF Interviews (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - 7023.52 Meteorological Data (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - 7023.53 Public Hearings (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - 7023.54 U.S. Fish & Wildlife (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - 7023.55 Development (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - 7023.56 CEQA process (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - 7023A MCP File Directory (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - 7023B Correspondence in (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - 7023C Correspondence out (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - 7023.1 Progress Reports/ Meeting Minutes #1 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - 7023.1 Progress Reports/ Meeting Minutes #2 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - 7023.4 Engineering & Design (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - 7023.2 Proposal/Scope (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - 7023.3A Land Use Permit Contract (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - 7023.3 Land Use Permit Assistance (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - 7023.5 Contract (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - 7023.5A Consulting (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - 7023.6 Articles (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - 7023.7 BAAQMD (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - 95019.2 SWRCB: EDCWA Reiner Supplement (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - 95019 SWRCB Testimony (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - 95019 Roberts To-Dos (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - 95019 Roberts Working Notes (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - 95019 EDCWA Reports 1992-1995 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Water publications (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - ICL (Institute for Conservation Leadership) 1995 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - ICL 9/1996 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - ICL To-Dos (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - ICL 1996 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - ICL Strategic Plan notes (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - ICL Board Meeting 3/1996 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - ICL Board Handbook 1995 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: memoranda, timesheets, etc (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: A-E miscellaneous 1991 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: F-L (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: M-R (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: S-Z (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: Expenses (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: Logs (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: Bank Statements & Checks (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: Payroll Taxes (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: Expenses (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: Timesheets (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: Bank (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - GEMS accounting 1990-1991: Paid Invoices (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - 05792.B Chevron Document Log 1993 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - 05792.00.000 General (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - 05792.00 Richmond Chevron (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - 05792.00.001 correspondence in (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - 05792.00.002 correspondence out (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - 05792.00.003 Regulatory Agency Correspondence (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - 05792.00.004 Articles (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - 05792.00.005 Teleconference logs (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - 05792.00.006 Publications (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - 05792.00.007 Faxes ESA-Chevron (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - 05792.00.008 Faxes Chevron-ESA (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - 05792.00.009 Faxes Richmond (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - 05792.00.010 PR (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - 05792.00.110 Contract (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - 05792.00.140 ESA Environmental Science workshop (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - 05792.00.200 Initial Study (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - 05792.00.300 Public Scoping meeting (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - 05792.00.301 EIR Permit mitigation strategy meeting (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - 05792.00.302 Health Risk Assessment (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - 05792.00.304 EIR Public Meetings (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - 05792.00.415 ESA proposal (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - 05792.00.417 Health Risk Assessment Protocol (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - 05792.00.421 Shell/Martinez documents (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - 05792.00.428 Preliminary Transportation Energy Demand (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - 05792.00.429 State BMP Project (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - 05792.00.430 Cumulative Impacts (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - 05792.00.430 Cumulative Impacts (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - 05792.00.431 Risk of Upset Study (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - 05792.00.432 WSA Traffic Study (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - 05792.00.434 Wildcat Marsh Enhancement Plan (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - 7023 MCP File Index (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - 7023 MCP Mitigation Measure Analysis Report Drafts (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - 00690 Russell Ranch Revised Impacts & Mitigation (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - 00690.92.10 Russell Ranch #1 1992 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - 00690.92.10 Russell Ranch #2 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - 05792.00.660 Roberts CEQA projects: Exxon Refinery Benicia CFP (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - 05792.00.670 General Chemical Company Spill (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - 05792.00.680 Chevron Draft EIR #1 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - 05792.00.680 Chevron Draft EIR #2 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - 05792.00.604 CEQA visual (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - 05792.00.605 CEQA Employment (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - 05792.00.606 CEQA Noise (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - 05792.00.607 CEQA Groundwater (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - 05792.00.608 CEQA Biology (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - 05792.00.610 CEQA emergency services (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - 05792.00.611 Public Health & Safety (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - 05792.00.630 ADEIR Preliminary Comments (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - 05792.00.650 Shell Refinery Martinez CFP (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - 05792.00.600d CEQA process #14 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - 05792.00.601 CEQA Air Quality (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - 05792.00.602 CEQA Geology (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - 05792.00.603 CEQA Hazardous (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - 05792.00.608 Blueprints (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - 05792.00.685 Conditions of Approval (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - 05792.00.685 Conditions of approval (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - 05792.00.690 Mitigation Monitoring Program (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - 05792.00.600a CEQA Process #1 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - 05792.00.600a CEQA Process #2 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 05792.00.600a CEQA Process #3 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - 05792.00 Environmental Questions for EIR (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - 7026.400 Sonoma LF General Service Tasks 1991 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - 7026.401 Presentation Development (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - 7026.402 Permitting Research (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - 7026.403 California Fish & Game (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - 7026.409 U.S. Army Corps of Engineers (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - 7026.500 Report & Drafts (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - 7026.500 Conditional Use Permit Application (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - 7026.510 CEQA Process (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - 7026.600 Stony Point Report & Miscellaneous (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - 7026.600 Wetlands Study (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - 7026.602 Site 33 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - 7026.604 MRF Environmental Assessment (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - 7026.700 Geotechnical Evaluation (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - 7026.800 Paleontology (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - 7026.950 Traffic (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - 7026.850 Archeology (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00693 RHAA Consulting 1993 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - GEMS accounts receivable 1991 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01090 B-PNL (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01492 Boreal (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01491 Bernau (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 06092 Theo Lacy (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01592 Del Webb (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01691 Chelshire Downs (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01992 Grass Valley (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 05192 Viborg (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 02592 Hungary EIA Class (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00491 EDCWA (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00190 Nevada County (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00190 HBA Contract (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01591 Myvatn (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 01791 77th Ave. (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 7026 Sonoma LF site 33 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 7023 MCP (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 7024 MCP (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 7036 MCP (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 893-7041 Kirby Canyon LF (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 893-6269 Industriplex (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 7040 MCP Permit (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: 00490 Siskiyou (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: M-70 Pipeline EIR (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: Humbug Creek/Willow Creek HBA Contract (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - GEMS accounts receivable: Humbug Creek/Willow Creek HBA Contract (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - California Solid Waste Disposal Testing Guidelines 1986 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Taiwan Construction & Planning report 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Taiwan E3 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Taiwan E4 1990 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Taiwan D3: Journals (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Taiwan D3: Photographs & Maps (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Taiwan D3: Miscellaneous notes (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Taiwan D3: Articles (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Taiwan D3: People (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Taiwan D3: Presentations (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Taiwan D3: Report Drafts (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Waste Management miscellaneous publications (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Solid Waste miscellaneous publications (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Geology miscellaneous publications (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - NAEP The Environmental Professional Vol. 18 #1 1996 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - UTR-CTC Statement of Qualifications 1993 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - CIS I 1993 Estonia (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - CIS I Russia/Belarus/Estonia Follow Up Correspondence (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - CIS I NAEP Russia Delegation (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - CIS II (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Brazil publications (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Canada A1 1984-1995 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - EIR Handbooks: Planning Economic Practices Manual (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - EIR Handbooks: Specific Plan Manual 1992 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - EIR Handbooks: Implementing Design in California Reader (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - EIR Handbooks: Sustainable Development (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - TDR Transfer of Development Rights (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Animal Control – Gulls memoranda and audiocassette (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - World Bank publications 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - 92026 CEC 1992 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - 92030 Kishirev Molova (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - 92031 Finland (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - 92032 Hawaii (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - 92033 NBD: Slovenia EIR course (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - 92035 NBD: Asia (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - 92035 NBD: Wyoming (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - 92037 CEC Environmental Services (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - 92037 CEC proposal (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - 92039 McClellan Cleanup (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - 92042 Yosemite Institute (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - 92043 SMUD Cogeneration (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - 92045 Poland (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - 00690 City of Folsom File Index (Box 68, Folder 20)
  - 00690.01.1 Easy Area Facilities Plan EIR (EAFP) #1 1991-1992 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  - 00690.01.1 EAFP #2 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  - 00690.01.1 EAFP #3 (Box 68, Folder 23)
  - 00690.01.1 EAFP #4 (Box 68, Folder 24)
  - 00690.01.1 EAFP #5 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - 00690.01.1 EAFP #6 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - 00690.01.1 EAFP #7 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - 00690 EAFP analysis EIR 1990 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - 00690.01.3 Wetlands (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - 00690.01 Report, Aerial Photographs, etc. (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - 00690.01.4 Broadstone II EIR (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - World Bank publications 1994-1996 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - World Bank publications 1994-1996 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - 7023E MCP DIP Graphic Materials (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - 7023.30 Water Tank Screening (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - 7023.31 Weed Monitoring (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - 7023.32 Wildlife management (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - 7023.33 Oak Woodlands Program (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - 7023.34 Wetlands Enhancement (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - 7023.35 Red Legged Frog (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - 7023.36 Bridge Crossing (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - 7023.37 Wildlife Surveys (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - 7023.38 Wildlife Fencing (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - 7023.39 Litter control (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - 7023.40 Emergency Plan (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - 7023.41 Employee Training (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - 7023.42 Equipment maintenance (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - 7023.43 Cultural Resources (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - 7023.44 Transportation & Circulation (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - 7023.45 Clayton mobile home Park & Recreation (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - 7023.46 Site Services & Utilities (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - 7023.47 Reduction & Resource Recovery (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - 7023.48 Construction Phasing (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - 7023.49 Closure/Post-Closure Maintenance (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - 7026A Sonoma 7026.A-109 File Index (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - 7026B Progress Reports (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - 7026C Contract (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - 7026C Technical Services Agreement (Box 71, Folder 9)
  - 7026D Correspondence out (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - 7026E Correspondence in (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - 7026F Change Order (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - 7026G News Articles (Box 71, Folder 13)
  - 7026.100 Biotic (Box 71, Folder 14)
  - Orange County Jail Expansion ER 1989 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - OC Respondents/Defendants Trial Brief (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - OC Plaintiffs/Petitioners Trial Brief (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - OC Meeting Notes 181, 1983, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - 00293 Memoranda, notes, etc. 1990-1992 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - 00293 Memoranda, notes, etc. 1986-1992 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Slovakia publications (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Sweden publications (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Mexico publications (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Pacific Rim publications (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - International – Other publications (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - 7023 MCP 22-36 File Index (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - 7023.22 SWRCB #1 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - 7023.22 SWRCB #2 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - 7023.22a Water Rights Issues (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - 7023.23 Initial Study (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - 7023.24 Issues (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - 7023.25 EIR introduction (Box 73, Folder 9)
  - 7023.26 EIR project description (Box 73, Folder 10)
  - 7023.27 EIR setting, impact (Box 73, Folder 11)
  - 7023.28 EIR draft vol.1 (Box 73, Folder 12)
  - 7023.29 Notice of Preparation Responses (Box 73, Folder 13)
  - 7023.30 EIR comments (Box 73, Folder 14)
  - 7023.31 Technical Background Report (Box 73, Folder 15)
  - 7023.32 EIR graphics (Box 73, Folder 16)
  - 7023.33 Sacramento River Toxic Chemical Risk Assessment (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - 7023.34 Comparison Charts (Box 73, Folder 18)